
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Containers>
  <Date>2021-02-11</Date>
  <Beta>False</Beta>
  <Category>HomeAutomation Tools</Category>
  <Name>ZWaveJS2MQTT</Name>
  <Project>https://github.com/zwave-js/zwavejs2mqtt</Project>
  <Overview>
   Fully configurable Zwave to MQTT Gateway and Control Panel.
  </Overview>
  <Description>
    Configurable Zwave to Mqtt Gateway
    Home Assistant integration (beta)
    Zwave Control Panel:
    Nodes management: check all nodes discovered in the z-wave network, send/receive nodes values updates directly from the UI and send action to the nodes and controller for diagnostics and network heal
    Custom Node naming and Location: Starting from v1.3.0 nodes name and location are stored in a JSON file named nodes.json. This because not all nodes have native support for naming and location features (#45). This change is back compatible with older versions of this package: on startup it will get all nodes names and location from the zwcfg_homeHEX.xml file (if present) and create the new nodes.json file based on that. This file can be imported/exported from the UI control panel with the import/export buttons placed on the top of nodes table, on the right of controller actions select.
    Firmware updates: You are able to send firmware updates to your devices using the UI, just select the controller action Begin Firmware Update
    Groups associations: create associations between nodes (also supports multi-instance associations, need to use last version of zwave-js)
    Custom scenes management
    Log debug in UI
    Mesh graph showing devices neighbors
  </Description>
  <Registry>https://hub.docker.com/r/zwavejs/zwavejs2mqtt</Registry>
  <GitHub>https://github.com/SiwatINC/unraid-ca-repository</GitHub>
  <Repository>https://hub.docker.com/r/zwavejs/zwavejs2mqtt</Repository>
  <Support>https://forums.unraid.net/topic/75588-support-siwats-docker-repository/</Support>
  <BindTime>true</BindTime>
  <Privileged>false</Privileged>
  <Environment>
  </Environment>
  <Data>
  </Data>
  <Config Name="Config Directory" Target="/usr/src/app/store" Default="/mnt/user/appdata/zwavejs2mqtt" Mode="rw" Description="This is the mnt directory of your unraid server&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Container path: /mnt" Type="Path" Display="advanced-hide" Required="true" Mask="false"/>
  <Config Mask="false" Required="true" Display="always" Type="Device" Description="ls /dev/serial/by-id/" Mode="" Default="" Target="" Name="Dongle">/dev/serial/by-id/usb-0658_0200-if00</Config>
  <Networking>
    <Mode>bridge</Mode>
  </Networking>
  <DonateText>If you like it, then consider buying me a soda as I don't like beer :P</DonateText>
  <DonateLink>https://www.paypal.me/siwatsirichai</DonateLink>
  <DonateImg>https://www.paypal.com/en_US/i/btn/btn_donate_SM.gif</DonateImg>
  <Banner></Banner>
  <Icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SiwatINC/unraid-ca-repository/master/icons/zwavejs2mqtt.png</Icon>
</Containers>
